<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Mom's Connection Doula Services</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Mom's Connection Doula Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://momsconnection.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mom's Connection Doula Services</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/sections/moms-connection-doula-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://momsconnection.net/sections/moms-connection-doula-services/</guid><description/></item><item><title>My Story</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/my-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://momsconnection.net/my-story/</guid><description>Hello! My name is Karen, and I am a certified birth and postpartum doula, connecting families through birth. I offer doula services in the Anderson, Knox, Morgan, and Roane Counties. I am passionate about mothers, babies, and family. I also have a deep desire to empower women through positive experiences of pregnancy, labor, childbirth, and the postpartum period.
I was born and raised in NH and moved to TN in 2009.</description></item><item><title>What's a Doula?</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/what/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://momsconnection.net/what/</guid><description>A doula is a trained professional who provides continuous physical, emotional and informational support to a mother before, during and shortly after childbirth to help her achieve the healthiest, most satisfying experience possible.
Always Empowering — We work to lift people up and enrich the lives others while always celebrating their individuality and uniqueness.
Always Investing — We invest in creating meaningful and lasting relationships with our clients and our community.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://momsconnection.net/services/</guid><description>Mom&amp;rsquo;s Connection Doula Services supports hospital, birth center, and home births in the Knoxville area. We support all of your family’s birth and baby choices and will help your family gain understanding and confidence during this amazing and exciting time. We can offer daytime and overnight postpartum care. We will offer care for singles, multiples, first babies, and larger families. We support your entire family to make the transition as positive and low stress as possible.</description></item><item><title>Helpful Links</title><link>https://momsconnection.net/helpful-links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://momsconnection.net/helpful-links/</guid><description>Awareness! August is National Breastfeeding Awareness Month!!
Online support for postpartum, helps when folks say “how can I help?”
https://www.giveinkind.com
Online meal train for postpartum period:
https://www.takethemameal.com
Journal Articles on Doulas Impact of Doulas on Healthy Birth Outcomes: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3647727/
Continuous Labor Support: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/28681500
Popular Labor Contraction Apps Contraction Master This app works with iOS or Android as well as web-based. If you are using the computer version, you do not need to be hooked up to the internet once the program has loaded.</description></item></channel></rss>